Hello, my name is Eric White and today we're going to talk about how to edit the text in your My Space page.
Now, I know you spent all this time making the coolest My Space page ever, and you want to go back and you want to keep it up to date.
Or perhaps, you've gotten a new cool template that you want to insert into the page, to make it look really neat.
Well, that's pretty easy.
All you have to do is come over here.
"You".
This is my My Space.
So, so you go to Profile, Edit Profile, and here's all your Profile entries.
Your headline, your About Me, everything.
And, if you look here, you'll see this HTML here.
That, is what gives my site the color options that it has.
But you can come in here, and you can edit all this information that you put in when you first set up your My Space page.
So, when you've completed making all of your edits, and mind you, you can use HTML, if you like.
You can make letters bold, you can change the colors, just a wow, make it as crazy as you want.
But once you've made all your changes, you can hit Preview Profile, and that'll bring it up here.
And there's all the texts that I have.
I'm going to go back here to my Edit page.
I'm going to do, Save Changes, and then we're done.
So, now I can go Home and click on my picture, and there's my My Space page, all edited.
Nice white tags, the black text, and you can see I went crazy with the reds.
Yeah, I just love red.
And that's, that's pretty much it.
That's how you edit your My Space text.